Hi, in this lesson, I will help you set up a Hip-Hop Pilot and Windows Studio Code.
Hip-Hop Pilot is assistant and to use it, you will need to have Hip-Hop Account and
Windows Studio Code editor.
If you don't have Hip-Hop Account, please visit a second resource for this lesson.
You will be redirected to the Hip-Hop Website.
Hip-Hop, it's a storage for your code, it's called Repository, you can find the other
code in this repository, you can store your code, you can share your code with the rest
of developers, so it's really popular platform for developers.
And you can click on sign-up, button, and just enter your data and create your account.
Okay, now we need to help with those to your code.
If you don't have it, please visit the next link from the resources.
You'll see the resource to your code website, it is a resource to the code interface from
the right side, you see the Hip-Hop Pilot chart in the middle, you see an open file with
the code, and by the left side you see the side bar with all the files you have and the
folder.
So you can click just on download button, you see it suggest me download it for my
course, because I'm using my course.
If you're using Windows or Linux, it will, you will see a different title, you just click
on this button and download your style.
If you see the wrong link or it doesn't detect your platform correctly, you can click
on other platforms linked, and you can choose whatever you need.
Okay, after you install it, please back to the instruction.
Okay, as you see, for people who don't have Hip-Hop Power subscription, you can
use it Hip-Hop Pilot for free.
Of course, with some limitations and some limited chart interactions.
And if you scroll down, you will see an instruction how to set up and Visual Studio
Code.
In Visual Studio Code, you need to click on compile at icon and click set up compiled,
and you will need to sign up to his hub.
Of course, authorize your access and then you will be able to use it.
I will show you how to do it.
I am clicking on an icon, I don't have any Hip-Hop Pilot plugin, I'm not sign it in, or
you will see everything from scratch, and I click on set-up compiled.
Do you see it asking me to sign in to the Hip-Hop?
And I need to click sign in.
I also have an option sign in with Hip-Hop Account, or sign in with GHE.com account,
I don't know what is it, so I'm using the Hip-Hop Account.
When you see, I already logged in, that is why I just click continue, it identifies my
account correctly.
And then you suggest open Visual Studio Code again.
And you see it wasn't started, I see the compiler chart at the right side.
Also, if I am clicking on extensions, I will see it from the left side, it took extension,
the choice of the Hip-Hop compiled, and the second one is a chart, and you can use it.
Okay, also, when you click on this icon, you do see your limits, as you see, I am above
the limit, I'm almost above the limit, because my code compilations use on 83% so it means
I use almost 2,000 compilations, but that messages I can still use.
And you can hear and enable the code compilations, and next add suggestions, if you want
to use it.
Okay, and now your component works, I suggest to back to the instruction and just to discuss
some edge cases.
So if you want to use a different Hip-Hop account to be your compiler, you can just click
on your user icon, sign out from your Hip-Hop account, and sign in to another account.
So you can just click on here, and you see it's my account, and I just click sign out.
Okay, if you need to Hip-Hop Pilot in Visual Studio Code, you can also find how to do it.
And you can also disable Co-Pilot of Workspace, because for example, you might want to work
it on personal projects, but your company won't allow you to work with Co-Pilot, because
I know some privacy, etc., and you might need to disable it for some workspaces.
Or you might disable it, or just disable it and enable it for some particular workspaces.
So it's the way how you can do it.
Okay, I hope it was really useful to you, and see you in the next lesson.